{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.5.4","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":540,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":10,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si5503","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5510","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Question 1: Who led the Israelites out of Egypt?  (Select your answer below.) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5517","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5525","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5529","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Moses ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5525_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Moses\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si5536","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5540","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"the Apostle John ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5536_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"the Apostle John\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7164","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7168","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Saul of Tarsus  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7164_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saul of Tarsus \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5675","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5473q0","for":"Slide5473q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5692","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5473q0","for":"Slide5473q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5705","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5473q0","for":"Slide5473q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5544","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You got it! Way to go! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5473q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"That is not the correct answer, but good try! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5473q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5570","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Please select an answer before moving on.   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5473q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5473","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si5503","si5510","si5529","si5540","si7168","si5675","si5692","si5705","si5570"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5473"},"question":{"interactionId":"5490","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Question 1: Who led the Israelites out of Egypt? \r(Select your answer below.)\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si8340","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8352","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_56","title":"Question 2: What was the name of the sea that God parted so Moses  and the Israelites could cross it?   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8396","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27","roles":{}},{"id":"si8363","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8367","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","title":"The Mediterranean Sea ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8363_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"36","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Mediterranean Sea\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8374","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8378","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"The Black Sea ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8374_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"38","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Black Sea\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8385","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8389","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"The Red Sea ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8385_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"40","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Red Sea\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si8513","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_17","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8551q1","for":"Slide8551q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8525","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8551q1","for":"Slide8551q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8537","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8551q1","for":"Slide8551q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8427","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":"You got it! Way to go! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8551q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_22","title":"That is not the correct answer, but good try! Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8551q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"Please select an answer before moving on.   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8551q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8551","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si8340","si8352","si8367","si8378","si8389","si8513","si8525","si8537","si8477"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8551"},"question":{"interactionId":"8325","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Question 2: What was the name of the sea that God parted so Moses \rand the Israelites could cross it?  \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["3"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si8588","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_57","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8600","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_58","title":"Question 3: What did Moses see on Mount Herob? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8644","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27_28","roles":{}},{"id":"si8611","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8615","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"The Red Sea ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8611_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"36_41","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Red Sea\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8622","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8626","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_71","title":"The golden calf ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8622_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"38_42","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The golden calf\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8633","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_72","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8637","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":"The Burning Bush ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8633_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"40_43","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Burning Bush\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si8761","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_18","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8799q2","for":"Slide8799q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8773","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8799q2","for":"Slide8799q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8785","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8799q2","for":"Slide8799q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8675","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":"You got it! Way to go! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8799q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8694","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_25","title":"That is not the correct answer, but good try! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8799q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8725","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"Please select an answer before moving on.   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8799q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8799","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si8588","si8600","si8615","si8626","si8637","si8761","si8773","si8785","si8725"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8799"},"question":{"interactionId":"8573","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Question 3: What did Moses see on Mount Herob?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["3"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si8881","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_59","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8893","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"Question 4: Moses, although Hebrew, grew up as an____________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8937","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27_29","roles":{}},{"id":"si8904","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8908","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","title":"Italian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8904_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"36_44","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Italian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8915","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_77","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8919","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":"Egyptian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8915_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"38_45","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Egyptian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si8926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_79","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8930","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","title":"Frenchman ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8926_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"40_46","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Frenchman\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9054","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9092q3","for":"Slide9092q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9066","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9092q3","for":"Slide9092q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9078","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9092q3","for":"Slide9092q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"You got it! Way to go! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9092q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8987","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":"That is not the correct answer, but good try! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9092q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9018","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":"Please select an answer before moving on.   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9092q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9092","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si8881","si8893","si8908","si8919","si8930","si9054","si9066","si9078","si9018"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9092"},"question":{"interactionId":"8866","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Question 4: Moses, although Hebrew, grew up as an____________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si9129","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9141","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"Question 5: Where was Moses found as a baby by the  Pharoah’s daughter? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27_30","roles":{}},{"id":"si9152","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9156","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_85","title":"In a boat on the Red Sea ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9152_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"36_47","roles":{"answer":{"title":"In a boat on the Red Sea\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_86","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9167","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_87","title":"Floating in a basket on the Nile River ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9163_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"38_48","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Floating in a basket on the Nile River\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si9174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_88","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_89","title":"In a stable in a manger ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9174_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"40_49","roles":{"answer":{"title":"In a stable in a manger\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9302","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_20","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9340q4","for":"Slide9340q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9314","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9340q4","for":"Slide9340q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9340q4","for":"Slide9340q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9216","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":"You got it! Way to go! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9340q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9235","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":"That is not the correct answer, but good try! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9340q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9266","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":"Please select an answer before moving on.   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9340q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9340","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si9129","si9141","si9156","si9167","si9178","si9302","si9314","si9326","si9266"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9340"},"question":{"interactionId":"9114","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Question 5: Where was Moses found as a baby by the \rPharoah’s daughter?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si9377","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_91","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9389","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_92","title":"Question 6: What was the name of Moses’s brother? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27_31","roles":{}},{"id":"si9400","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_93","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9404","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_94","title":"Aaron ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9400_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"36_50","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Aaron\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si9411","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_95","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_96","title":"Peter ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9411_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"38_51","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Peter\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9422","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_97","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9426","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","title":"Paul ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9422_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"40_52","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Paul\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9550","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_21","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9588q5","for":"Slide9588q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9562","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9588q5","for":"Slide9588q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9588q5","for":"Slide9588q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9464","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":"You got it! Way to go! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9588q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9483","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":"That is not the correct answer, but good try! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9588q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9514","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":"Please select an answer before moving on.   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9588q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9588","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si9377","si9389","si9404","si9415","si9426","si9550","si9562","si9574","si9514"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9588"},"question":{"interactionId":"9362","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Question 6: What was the name of Moses’s brother?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si9625","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9637","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"Question 7: What happened in ancient Egypt because the Pharoah would not free the Israelites from slavery?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9681","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27_32","roles":{}},{"id":"si9648","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9652","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_103","title":"God allowed ten plagues to be visited upon ancient Egypt.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9648_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"36_53","roles":{"answer":{"title":"God allowed ten plagues to be visited upon ancient Egypt. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si9659","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9663","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","title":"There was an earthquake and a tsunami.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9659_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"38_54","roles":{"answer":{"title":"There was an earthquake and a tsunami. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9670","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9674","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Nothing happened to the people of ancient Egypt.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9670_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"40_55","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nothing happened to the people of ancient Egypt. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9798","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9836q6","for":"Slide9836q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9810","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9836q6","for":"Slide9836q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9822","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9836q6","for":"Slide9836q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9712","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":"You got it! Way to go! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9836q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9731","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_37","title":"That is not the correct answer, but good try! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9836q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9762","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_38","title":"Please select an answer before moving on.   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9836q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9836","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si9625","si9637","si9652","si9663","si9674","si9798","si9810","si9822","si9762"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9836"},"question":{"interactionId":"9610","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Question 7: What happened in ancient Egypt because the Pharoah would\rnot free the Israelites from slavery? \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si9873","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_109","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9885","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_110","title":"Question 8: What did Moses chisel in to stone tablets?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9929","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27_33","roles":{}},{"id":"si9896","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_111","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_112","title":"The Letter to the Seven Churches ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9896_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"36_56","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Letter to the Seven Churches\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9907","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_113","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9911","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_114","title":"The Ten Commandments, also called the Word of the Covenant.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9907_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"38_57","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Ten Commandments, also called the Word of the Covenant. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si9918","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_115","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9922","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_116","title":"The Book of John  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9918_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"40_58","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Book of John \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_23","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10084q7","for":"Slide10084q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10058","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10084q7","for":"Slide10084q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10070","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10084q7","for":"Slide10084q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9960","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_39","title":"You got it! Way to go! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10084q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_40","title":"That is not the correct answer, but good try! Click anywhere to continue.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10084q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10010","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_41","title":"Please select an answer before moving on.   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10084q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10084","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si9873","si9885","si9900","si9911","si9922","si10046","si10058","si10070","si10010"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10084"},"question":{"interactionId":"9858","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Question 8: What did Moses chisel in to stone tablets? \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_8","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12091","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5758","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5766","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5731","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Book of Exodus Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5754","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5762","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5786","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5790","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5807","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5717","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5717"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":" Want to learn more about the Book of Exodus in the Bible?   You can read the Bible online at www.bible.com or the Book of Exodus in your own Bible at home!  Click Exit below!     ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"EXIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10860","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"EXIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10872","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"EXIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10888","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_4","SmartShape_5","si10860","si10872"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10888"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"AExodusQuiz","class":"project","title":"AExodusQuiz","children":["Slide5473","Slide8551","Slide8799","Slide9092","Slide9340","Slide9588","Slide9836","Slide10084","Slide5717","Slide10888"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":false,"questions":["Slide5473q0","Slide8551q1","Slide8799q2","Slide9092q3","Slide9340q4","Slide9588q5","Slide9836q6","Slide10084q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":8,"passScore":7}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":false,"cc":true,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5473","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide8551","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide8799","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide9092","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide9340","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide9588","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide9836","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide10084","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide5717","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide10888","title":"Slide 10"}]}